let divisionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 18 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "4",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "5",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 14 ÷ 2",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 12 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "4",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 44 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 39 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 32 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 28 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 45 ÷ 15",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 32 ÷ 16",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "4",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 22 ÷ 11",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "10",
        correctAnswer: "2",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 42 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "4",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 64 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 72 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 90 ÷ 10",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "10",
        AnswerD: "11",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 80 ÷ 10",
        AnswerA: "7",
        AnswerB: "8",
        AnswerC: "9",
        AnswerD: "10",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 50 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "10",
        AnswerB: "11",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 81 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "10",
        AnswerD: "11",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 100 ÷ 10",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "20",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 88 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "14",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 63 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 70 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "10",
        AnswerD: "11",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 54 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "5",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "5",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 50 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "20",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 96 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "11",
        AnswerD: "12",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "5",
        AnswerD: "6",
        correctAnswer: "5",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 100 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "18",
        AnswerB: "20",
        AnswerC: "22",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "20",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 120 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 140 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 180 ÷ 10",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "20",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 150 ÷ 25",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "10",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 135 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "15",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 110 ÷ 11",
        AnswerA: "9",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "11",
        AnswerD: "12",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 121 ÷ 11",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "12",
        AnswerD: "13",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 144 ÷ 12",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "16",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 143 ÷ 13",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "14",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 76 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 78 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "26",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 108 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 128 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "14",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 129 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "23",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 78 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "9",
        AnswerB: "11",
        AnswerC: "12",
        AnswerD: "13",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 52 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 171 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "17",
        AnswerB: "19",
        AnswerC: "21",
        AnswerD: "23",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 153 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "14",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 174 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "29",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 144 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "15",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 95 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 162 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 168 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "14",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 111 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 228 ÷ 12",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 189 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 168 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 114 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 156 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 154 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "22",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 196 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 288 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "29",
        AnswerB: "31",
        AnswerC: "32",
        AnswerD: "33",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 296 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 224 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "29",
        AnswerB: "31",
        AnswerC: "32",
        AnswerD: "33",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 160 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "30",
        AnswerB: "35",
        AnswerC: "40",
        AnswerD: "45",
        correctAnswer: "40",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 188 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "46",
        AnswerB: "47",
        AnswerC: "48",
        AnswerD: "49",
        correctAnswer: "47",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 234 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "38",
        AnswerB: "39",
        AnswerC: "40",
        AnswerD: "41",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 210 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "20",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "30",
        AnswerD: "35",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 144 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 228 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "37",
        AnswerB: "38",
        AnswerC: "39",
        AnswerD: "40",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 312 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 324 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "34",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 405 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "43",
        AnswerB: "45",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "49",
        correctAnswer: "45",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 322 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "45",
        AnswerB: "46",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "46",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 225 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "27",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 336 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "46",
        AnswerB: "47",
        AnswerC: "48",
        AnswerD: "49",
        correctAnswer: "48",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 124 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "31",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 352 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "46",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "44",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 266 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 276 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "42",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "46",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "46",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 184 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "23",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 222 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 145 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "27",
        AnswerB: "28",
        AnswerC: "29",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "29",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 152 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "37",
        AnswerB: "38",
        AnswerC: "39",
        AnswerD: "40",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 168 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "24",
        AnswerD: "26",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 304 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "34",
        AnswerC: "36",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 282 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 315 ÷ 15",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 189 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 279 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "31",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 234 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
]